Hello and welcome to this introduction to SubTranslate.
Today, we're going to demonstrate how to translate subtitles automatically.
SubTranslate is a powerful tool that can translate subtitles between multiple languages.
It uses advanced AI to ensure translations are accurate and natural sounding.
You can choose between different translation styles, like literal or colloquial.
The system also maintains context between sentences for better coherence.
Additionally, you can customize the translation prompts to fit your specific needs.
For technical terms, you can provide a glossary to ensure consistent translations.
SubTranslate works with various subtitle formats and can be integrated into your workflow.
Thank you for watching this introduction. Let's see how it works in practice.